One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Army of One
Tek Kişilik Ordu
I can't believe they managed to restrain you, Master Sasaki.
Sasaki-sama, yakalanacağınız aklımıza gelmezdi.
Pretty dumb, right?
Ahmakça, değil mi?
I never thought Kyoshiro, my so-called friend, would trick me like this.
Güya en iyi arkadaşım olan Kyoshiro tarafından kandırıldım.
Now...
Ee...
What the hell caused this?
buraya ne oldu böyle?
Well, Big Mom was fighting in the dome...
Şey, Big Mom kule içinde saldırınca...
And her attack made it all the way out here?!
Saldırısı, duvarı mı deldi geçti yani?
That's some insane strength.
Nasıl bir güç böyle.
Well, at least it got me free.
Neyse, sayenizde kurtuldum.
Anyway, I can't believe Kyoshiro was one of Oden's retainers.
Ama hâlâ Kyoshiro'nun Oden'in hizmetkârı olduğuna inanamıyorum.
I don't give a rat's ass about Wano's history...
Wano'nun tarihi ilgimi çekmese de...
but he's going to regret double-crossing me!
bana ihanetinin günahı ağır!
Charge!
Saldırın!
We shall put an end to this!
Bu zulme burada bir son vereceğiz!
Exterminate the minks!
Minklerin kökünü kurutun!
You cannot break our will!
Minklerin azmi...
We will take you-gara down!
muhakkak siz-garalara üstün gelecektir!
Go ahead and do your worst.
Yapabiliyorsanız yapın da görelim!
This will finish you off!
Bununla bitecek!
Let us take care of the rest!
Öne çıkma vaktidir!
Wait.
Bekleyin.
Kin'emon.
Kin'emon.
Dog! Cat!
Inu, Neko!
Let us handle this.
Bunu bize bırakın.
Indeed.
Evet.
Such speed!
Hızlılar!
It's not just the Straw Hats...
Hasır Şapkalar değil yalnızca...
Those are totally Udon prisoners.
şuradakiler de kesinlikle Udon mahkûmları!
Even Hyogoro's down there!
Hyogoro bile burada!
What happened at the prisoner mining camp in Udon?
Udon tutsak madeninde neler olmuş böyle?
Did they threaten Babanuki?
Babanuki bize ihanet mi etti?
This is Warden Babanuki in Udon.
Müdür Babanuki, Udon'dan rapor veriyor.
Straw Hat Luffy, Captain Kid, and all the troublemakers are locked in their cells.
Hasır Şapkalı Luffy'yle Kaptan Kid ve bela çıkaran diğer herkes, hücreye tıkıldı.
So, I called to tell you all is well.
Yani burada durum kontrol altında.
This doesn't add up.
Bir terslik var!
I'm not going to blame you for all this.
Seni şimdi suçlamayacağım.
After all, you've always been brainless.
Sen eskiden beri beyinsizdin.
You didn't have to say all that other crap!
Tek kelimeyle ağzıma sıçtın, adi herif!
We need to take care of this situation immediately.
Bu durumu bir an önce düzeltmemiz gerek.
Now you sound like a leader!
Sonunda lider gibi konuştun!
Damn that Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka adisi!
Onigashima is in chaos...
Onigashima kaos içinde.
Hawkins.
Hawkins.
It wasn't your choice to join the Beast Pirates.
Canavar Korsanları'na istemeden dahil oldun.
If you're planning to defect, now's the time...
İhanet edeceksen şimdi vaktidir.
Are you really asking me to betray them?
İhanet etmem için beni teşvik mi ediyorsun?
I'm no fool.
Aptal değilim.
One percent.
Yüzde 1.
What are you trying to predict?
Ne öngörmeye çalışıyorsun?
The probability that a certain someone survives until tomorrow.
Belli bir adamın yarına dek hayatta kalma olasılığını.
Only one percent, huh...?
Yüzde 1 mi...?
Poor bastard.
Üzüldüm.
Come in, Soaring Six.
Toplanın, Tobi Roppo!
How annoying!
Sinir bozucu!
What do you want, King?!
Ne var, King?
Everyone...
Hepinizin...
As you know...
bildiği gibi...
the situation has changed.
durumlar değişti.
On the day of the annual Fire Festival,
Yılda bir kez yapılan Ateş Festivali gününde...
we let the Red Scabbards samurai, of all enemies, invade.
...düşmanımız olan Kızıl Kın samuraylarının istilasına engel olamadık.
This is the biggest blunder in Onigashima's history.
Onigashima tarihindeki en büyük fiyasko bu.
We must set aside our internal struggle, even if Kaido encouraged it.
Kaido-san'ın başlattığı aramızdaki şu çekişmeye son vermeliyiz.
Our what?
Çekişme mi?
This is regarding Young Master Yamato.
Genç Efendi Yamato ile ilgili olan.
The one who returns Young Master Yamato home...
Kayıp olan Genç Efendi Yamato'yu bulup getirenin...
earns the right to challenge any of the Superstars for their position.
Önder olabilmek için bize meydan okuma hakkı kazanması meselesi.
Although it pains me to say this,
Ben de bunu bekliyordum fakat...
we must put this on hold for the time being.
...şimdilik ertelememiz gerekiyor.
What?! Seriously?!
Ne?! Cidden mi?!
Of course.
Elbette.
Look around you, Big Sis.
Etrafına bir bak, abla.
Oh, Pay-Pay! Just who I was looking for!
Canım Pay-Pay'im! Tam da seni arıyordum!
Yamato got away by climbing the wall, so you have to give me a piggyback ride...
Yamato duvara tırmanarak kaçtığı için beni sırtında taşımanı bekliyordum!
No way.
Asla!
You have to!
Asla mı?
Shut up, you stupid kids.
Kesin sesinizi, adi veletler sizi!
– Who are you calling a kid?!
– Kime velet dedin sen?
I'm not a kid anymore! Don't call me that!
Ben velet değilim, bana velet deme!
Kaido is up on the rooftop.
Kaido-san çatıda.
The enemy is going to climb to the top of the castle from the inside.
Düşman, içeriden tırmarak yukarıya ulaşmaya çalışacak.
All of you will need to do whatever you can to stop them.
Her biriniz, kendi yöntemlerinizle onları engellemelisiniz.
Our troops number 30,000.
Bizim 30 bin askerimiz var.
Their troops only number 5,000.
İşgalcilerin sayısı ise 5 bin.
Still, don't underestimate them.
Ama yine de onları hafife almasanız iyi olur.
Good luck.
İyi şanslar.
Hey, Drake!
Hey, Drake!
There's an opportunity in all this mess.
Bu karmaşa bir fırsat,
Take a walk with me.
bana biraz eşlik et.
I can't handle it on my own.
Tek başıma altından kalkamam.
Where are you going?
Nereye gideceksin?
To kill the man I want to kill!
Öldürmek istediğim kişiyi öldürmeye.
Let's pay Queen a visit.
Queen'in yanına.
Don't get me involved in your little spat.
Kendi aranızdaki işlere beni bulaştırmayın.
Do you wanna weaken our forces?
Savaş gücümüzü azaltmak mı niyetin?
He's useless anyway.
Bir işe yaradığı yok zaten.
I'm not sure about this...
Ben öyle demezdim.
Straw Hats!
Hasır Şapka ve diğerleri!
Allow us to clear the way to the castle!
Kaleye giden yolu sizin için temizleyeceğiz!
Indeed! Conserve your strength for the battle ahead!
Gücünüzü boşa harcayıp da yorulmayın!
Charge!
İlerleyin!
Get Straw Hat and his allies into the castle!
Hasır Şapkalar için yolu açın!
Don't allow them to recover!
Heveslerini kırın!
They're just prisoners and yakuza!
Alt tarafı mahkûm ve yakuza onlar!
How amazingly chaotic.
Ne kargaşa ama.
We must eliminate the large one, as well!
Şu iriyi de indirmemiz lazım!
I can't believe such a human exists.
Böyle insanlar da varmış demek.
Do not hesitate! We must take him down!
Tereddüt yok! Onu indirmeliyiz!
Attack his feet!
Ayaklarına saldırın!
Oh my, that was close.
Amanın, kıl payıydı.
Jinbe!
Jinbe-san!
That's enough, you two.
Bu kadar yeter!
Kaido!
Kaido!
Jack is one of my handpicked Superstars!
Jack, bizzat benim seçtiğim bir Önder!
I won't just sit idly by as you beat one of my best men to death.
Değerli adamım öldürülürken sessiz kalıp izleyecek değilim!
Please... forgive me...
Özür... dilerim,
Viceroy Kaido...
Kaido-sama...
You're no weakling, Jack.
Zayıf olmadığını biliyorum.
It's just that these guys...
Sadece...
are too strong!
onlar çok güçlü!
Thanks to these Sulongs, we've taken serious losses...
Sulong formları yüzünden ciddi zayiat verdik.
But you did a good job fending them off as well as you did.
Ama o Sulong'ları bu noktaya kadar da iyi idare ettin.
Go get yourself patched up.
Git de baktır kendine,
You've already done plenty.
bu kadarı yeterli.
What the hell is going on?!
Ne demek oluyor bu?
You should be asking yourself that question!
Bunu bizim sormamız gerek.
You let Trafalgar Law escape in the Flower Capital, didn't you?
Çiçek Başkenti'nde, Trafalgar Law'ı sen serbest bıraktın.
We had a guard posted...
Oraya bir gardiyan dikmiştik...
I figured it must have been you.
Senden başkası olamaz, diye düşündüm.
What's your objective?
Amacın nedir?
I see...
Anlıyorum,
The one you wanted to kill is...
öldürmek istediğin kişi...
...you, you piece of shit!
Sendin işte, adi herif!
We should be ashamed that we had a rat among our ranks.
Aramızda böyle birinin olması bir utanç.
What are you up to?
Neyin peşindesin?
Are you working alone, or with a group?
İçimize sızan sadece sen miydin yoksa başkaları da mı var?
Just who exactly are you?!
Neyin nesisin sen?
I guess this is it...
İşler bu noktaya gelmişken...
I can't talk myself out of this.
bahane üretmek nafile.
Unfortunately...
Ne yazık ki...
I won't talk even if you kill me!
beni öldürseniz bile size hiçbir şey anlatmam.
Oh, I'm not gonna kill you...
Seni öldürmeyeceğiz!
My kind of torture will break your spirit instead.
İşkencemle iradeni yerle bir edeceğim!
Bet you can't wait, huh, Drake?
Sabırsızlanıyorsun, değil mi Drake?
Damn monster...
Şu canavar...
Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka-san!
That thing is just like Oars.
...aynı Oars'a benziyor.
Back then, it took all of us together to bring down something that huge!
Onun gibi büyük bir şeyi eskiden anca hep birlikte yenebilmiştik.
But things are different now!
Şimdi durum farklı!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Gear Fourth!
Dördüncü Vites!
Boundman!
Sıçrayan Adam!
Oh, he did it again!
Oh, işte yine!
That form... He looks just like a guardian deity!
O formu ile tam bir koruyucu tanrı gibi!
All right.
Pekâlâ.
Huh?!
Heh?!
What, not interested in the torture?
İşkence istemiyorsun demek?
What a bummer...
Yazık oldu!
Why don't I...
Bu...
leave you all...
zahmet verdiğim sizlere...
a parting gift?
bir hediyemdir!
Take cover!
Siper alın!
Now what? How do I get away?
Ne yapmalıyım, nasıl kaçacağım?
Is there no way back to the Marines?!
Artık Denizciler'e geri dönemem!
No!
Hayır!
No time to think about that now!
Bunu sonra düşünürüm!
There's still one hope left!
Hâlâ bir umut var!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Get out of my way...
Çekil yolumdan...
Juki!
Juki!
X...
X...
...Kong...
...Kong...
...Gun! ...Calibur!
...Silahı! ...Calibur!
That's...
O adam...
...Drake of the Soaring Six!
Tobi Roppo'dan Drake!
Why did he attack the giant?!
Neden deve saldırdı?!
There's still...
Hâlâ bir umut...
hope.
var!
Crap!
Hay lanet!
Luffy is amazing!
Luffy-san müthiştir!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Hasır Şapkalı Luffy!
I can't say why, but I've just become an army of one!
Bir sebepten, artık tek kişilik bir orduyum!
Please!
Lütfen...
Allow me to fight on your side!
yanınızda savaşmama izin ver!
Huh?!
Heh?!
What's with that guy?
Kimin nesi bu adam?
He wants to fight with us?!
Yanımızda savaşmak mı?
He's that perv who saw Nami and Robin taking a bath the other day in the Flower Capital!
O herif, geçen Çiçek Başkenti'nde Nami-san'la Robin-chan'ı banyoda gözetleyen sapık!
He just turned into some kind of dinosaur!
O herif hakikaten de az önce dinazor gibi bir şeye dönüştü!
He must be one of those Soaring Six officers.
Tobi Roppo elemanlarından biri olmalı.
But... something's strange...
Ama garip.
What in the world does he think he's doing?!
Ne yaptığını sanıyor bu?
Hey, Drake!
Hey, Drake!
Why did you attack one of the Numbers?!
Ne diye bir Numbers'a saldırdın?
Luffy is amazing!
Luffy-san müthiştir!
He just makes you feel like...
Luffy-san öyle biri ki...
like you're super close if you're friends,
arkadaşlarını çok yakınında tutar...
but if you become his enemy, he'll leave you in the dust.
ama düşmanları ona ulaşamaz bile!
That's the kind of guy he is!
Luffy-san böyle biri işte!
What do you mean?
Ne demek istiyorsun?
Luffy has this aura that draws people to him!
Luffy-san'ın insanları kendine çeken bir aurası var!
I know you!
Seni tanıyorum!
You wanna take down Kaido too?!
Sen de mi Kaido'nun peşindesin?!
I can't tell you why, but we have the same goal!
Nedenini söyleyemem ama amacımız aynı!
Don't try to pull anything on us right now!
Şu noktada boktan bir numara bize sökmez!
Luffy!
Luffy!
He's working for Kaido now, just like Hawkins!
Hawkins gibi, o da Kaido'nun astı!
I was just removed from my position!
Ama şu an o konumla işim bitti!
That's why you wanna side with us?!
Bittiği için mi yanımızda olmak istiyorsun?
How can we trust that two-timer?!
Böyle iki yüzlü birisine güvenir miyiz hiç?
Stay away from Luffy, X Drake!
Luffy'den uzak dur, X. Drake!
Even the world of pirates is governed by a code of honor!
Korsanların dünyasında bile ahlak vardır!
Sure, we can team up.
Pekâlâ, müttefik olabiliriz.
– No way!
– Hayatta olmaz!
Stay out of this, Captain! You're such a dumbass!
Kapa' çeneni, Kaptan! Seni ahmak!
Hurry to the castle, Luffy!
Bir an önce kaleye gidin, Luffy!
Okay!
Olur!
I'll leave them to you!
Burası sizde!
Sanji! Let's get inside the castle!
Sanji, kalenin içine gidiyoruz!
Yeah!
Evet!
The man in the straw hat...
Hasır şapkalı adam...
I guess he's the boss of all these pirates and samurai!
Korsanların ve samurayların patronu oymuş gibi görünüyor.
Let's go, Big Sis!
Gidelim, abla!
Keep those two away from Straw Hat!
Bu ikisini, Luffy-san'a yaklaştırmayacağız!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
Move it, samurai!
Çekilin, samuray bozuntuları!
You ultra-incompetent bumbling buffoons!
Sizi beceriksiz soytarılar sizi!
I fought those two in the castle!
Kalenin içinde dövüştüğüm ikili bunlar!
That's...
Şu adam...
the dinosaur from the Flower Capital!
Çiçek Başkenti'ndeki dinazor!
But...
İyi de...
who's that cutie right beside him?!
yanındaki şu tatlış da kim?
You'll never see Kaido again!
Kaido-san'ı bir daha görebileceğini düşünme sakın...
Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka!
Lethal... Green Star!
Ölümcül... Yeşil Yıldız!
Skull Bombgrass!
Patlayan Kurukafa Otu!
Pay-Pay!
Pay-Pay!
Wh-Who is that?!
K-Kim o?
I'm Nami!
Ben Nami!
What's your problem?!
Sen de kimsin be?
Nothing I like more than exterminating lizards.
Kertenkelelerin kökünü kazımaya bayılırım!
Now prepare yourself!
O yüzden, hazırla kendini!
What the hell are you doing?!
Ne yapıyorsun sen be?
Lizards?!
Kertenkele mi dedin?
Prepare to be sprayed with lizard killer!
Şimdi üzerine kertenkele ilacı sıkacağım!
Don't hide!
Saklanmasana be!
How dare you shoot me!
Yapacağınızı yaptınız!
Just who the hell did that?!
Kimdi o?
Oh, Pay-Pay!
Oh, Pay-Pay!
It was that detestable tramp!
Şu kadındı-arinsu!
That's right!
Doğru!
I am the Great Lizard Buster, Nami!
Benim adım, Kertenkele Avcısı Nami!
Remember my name!
Unutmayın bu adı!
Knock it off already!
Sus dedim sana!
It wasn't me, but whatever!
Ben değildim ama fark etmez artık!
The battle is already on!
Savaş zaten başlamış durumda!
Now...
Şimdi...
Bring it on!
gelin de görelim!
What?!
Ne?!
Your words don't match your actions!
Yaptığınla dediğin birbirini tutmuyor!
Look who's talking!
Sen hiç konuşma!
I won't let you get away!
Kaçamayacaksınız!
How could you hurt Pay-Pay?!
Ne cüretle Pay-Pay'e...
Look...
Bizim...
...how fast...
kaçmalarımızı...
– ...we can run away!
– ...hafife almayın!
– Hold it!
– Bekleyin!
– Stop!
– Durun!
I'm counting on you, Usopp!
Sana güveniyorum, Usopp!
Protect my Nami!
Canım Nami-san'ımı koru!
Come on, Luffy! Let's meet up with Kin'emon's group!
Hadi, Luffy! Kin'emon'ların olduğu yere gidelim!
Yeah!
Tamam!
Hey, Sanji!
Hey, Sanji!
Cover your ears!
Kulaklarını kapat!
O-Okay!
T-Tamam!
Let's drop a battle beat!
Savaş müziğime kulak verin!
Slash!
Kes!
SLASH
KES
Looks like you wised up, Straw Hat!
Sanki biraz akıllanmışsın, Hasır Şapka!
But...
Ama...
it's gonna be tough to fight if you can't hear!
işitmeden savaşmak biraz zor olacak!
Check it out!
Kulak ver!
Scratchmen Apoo (Captain of the On Air Pirates) Informant to the Beast Pirates Bounty: 350 Million Berries
Scratchmen Apoo (Canlı Yayın Korsanlarının Kaptanı) Canavar Korsanlarının Muhbiri Kelle Ödülü: 350 Milyon Beli
Jaki!
Jaki!
Goki!
Goki!
Juki!
Juki!
It's too painful to see you guys like this!
Bu ne acı verici bir manzara böyle!
Th-The ten of you...
S-Siz onunuz...
have leveled countless towns together!
bir sürü şehri yakıp yıkmamış mıydınız?
That's why...
Yani kalkıp...
it's just not fair to get your asses kicked while drunk...
şu güzelim ziyafette sarhoşken benzetilmek...
at such a delightful banquet!
size hiç yakışmadı!
Right?!
Değil mi?!
Don't you think so... Haccha?!
Haksız mıyım... Haccha?!
Are you sobered up now?!
İyice ayıldın mı?
There are ten of them?!
Bunlardan 10 tane mi varmış?!
I'm gonna need more cola!
Kolam yetmeyecek!
There's always strength in numbers!
Ne olursa olsun, her biri bir tehdit!
Time to teach these lousy fools...
Antik bir dev sahiden kızdığında...
what happens when an ancient giant loses their cool!
neler olurmuş, göster şunlara!
What?! Is he their tamer or something?
Ne, onların eğitmeni falan mı bu?
That jerk!
Seni adi...
Forget about it!
Boş ver!
We gotta go!
Gitmemiz gerek!
Fine!
Anladım!
Let's go!
Gidelim!
Yeah!
Tabii!
It's just about showtime!
Şov zamanı, açın perdeleri!
No room for you guys on stage!
Sahnede size yer yok...
This is a solo performance!
bu tek kişilik bir gösteri!
Don't stop, Luffy!
Durma, Luffy!
Yeah, I got it!
Anladım!
Look how strong he is!
Nasıl bir güçtür bu?!
Don't tell me he's going to use his ally as a weapon!
Yoldaşını silah olarak mı kullanacak yoksa?
Oh no!
Eyvah!
Franky! Run straight out of the dome!
Franky, doğruca kubbenin dışına doğru koş!
If we let this monstrosity run amok any longer, the samurai will be overwhelmed!
O şey burada kontrolden çıkarsa samuraylar buna dayanamaz!
Sure thing!
Anladım!
I'm counting on you!
Sana güveniyorum!
Yeah!
Tabii!
Does he think the General Franky is some kind of action figure?!
General Franky'yi oyuncak falan mı zannediyor bu?
You're not getting your grubby hands on me!
Yakalanır mıyım sandın?
He's gonna regret...
Beni oyuncak sandığına...
treating it like a toy!
pişman edeceğim seni!
At the very least...
En azından...
it's a much better outcome for me if you guys win.
sizin kazanmanız, benim işime daha çok gelir!
Is that convincing enough?!
Bu yetmez mi?
I see.
Anlıyorum.
You're pretty straightforward.
Hiç lafı dolandırmıyorsun.
But...
Ama...
you're still hiding your identity!
kimliğini hâlâ saklıyorsun!
We can't fight with a guy like that!
Böyle biriyle sırt sırta savaşamayız!
I just got a good idea!
İyi bir fikir düştü aklıma!
Let's call in a few more Numbers!
Daha fazla Numbers çağıralım hadi!
Hey, guys!
Hey, çocuklar!
Sober up and get over here!
Ayılın ve buraya gelin!
Knock that shit off!
Kes şu zırvalığı!
Yo, yo! I heard about you, Drake!
Yo, yo! Söylenenleri duydum, Drake!
Are you gonna leech off that itty-bitty pirate crew now?!
Bu defa da şu küçük korsan grubunu mu karıştıracaksın?
Scratchmen Apoo!
Scratchmen Apoo!
I've always hated this guy!
Bu heriften hep nefret etmişimdir!
I'll kick his ass, but I'm not doing it for you guys!
Onun canına okuyacağım ama sizin için değil!
What's this? Common ground?
Ne bu? Ortak nokta mı?
I don't like him either.
Ben de ondan hoşlanmıyorum.
Looks like... we've got an alliance!
O zaman birlikte çalışalım!
What the heck?!
Ne dedin?!
Drake!
Drake!
Don't think you can get away, you traitor!
Kaçabileceğini sanma, seni hain!
I mean, you gotta be a spy!
Yoksa casus mu demeliyim?
You've got another freak coming after you...
Yine ucubenin biri, peşine düşmüş gibi.
Did you think that crap would be enough to take me down?
Böyle birine yenileceğimi mi düşündün?
Ow, ow, ow...
Of, of, of...
Hey, stay with me!
Hey, dayan biraz!
Ouch! Dammit!
Acıyor, kahretsin!
You're okay!
İyi misin,
It's a shallow wound!
yaran derin değil!
Is this...?!
Bu...
Don't tell me...
Yoksa...
this bullet...
bu mermiler...
Now... scamper around, exhaust your strength, then die!
Şimdi, kaçmaktan yorulduğunuz için öleceksiniz!
I can't wait to see how many you can dodge!
Kaç kez savuşturacaksınız, görelim!
The thought never crossed my mind.
Bunu düşünmedim bile!
Blast Breath!
Patlayan Nefes!
Foxfire Style...
Tilki Ateşi Stili...
Flame-Rend!
Alev Yaran!
You thought we would flee?
Kaçmak mı?
How amusing!
Güldürme bizi!
We are done running!
Kaçmaktan gına geldi!
And done hiding!
Saklanmaktan gına geldi!
Let us die as Lord Oden's samurai!
Bırak da Oden-sama'nın samurayları olarak can verelim!
Firmly grasping your severed head!
Kelleni de yanımıza alarak elbet!